#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/khyatti (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Matlab

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Office

### **Publications**

Insights from Building an Open-Ended Conversational Agent Using AI to Design Stone Jewelry

# Khyatti Gupta

Software Engineer 3 at Google | Microsoft | IIT Delhi Bengaluru

## Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), C++, Matlab, Microsoft Excel, and Microsoft Office. Strong engineering professional with a Integrated M.Tech focused in Mathematics and Computing from Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi.

## Experience

Google
Software Engineer 3
September 2019 - Present (1 year)

Bengaluru Area, India

Microsoft

3 years 2 months

Software Engineer 2 March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Software Engineer

July 2016 - February 2019 (2 years 8 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

ARP Research LLP

Quantitative Analyst May 2015 - July 2015 (3 months)

Microsoft India Software Development Engineer Intern May 2014 - July 2014 (3 months)

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi Integrated M.Tech, Mathematics and Computing · (2011 - 2016)